export const HistQuestions = [{
        prompt: "1. World War I began in which year?",
        optionA: "1923",
        optionB: "1938",
        optionC: "1917",
        optionD: "1914",
        answer: "1914",
        number: "1",
    },
    {
        prompt: "2. Adolf Hitler was born in which country?",
        optionA: "France",
        optionB: "Germany",
        optionC: "Austria",
        optionD: "Hungary",
        answer: "Austria",
        number: "2",
    },
    {
        prompt: "3. John F. Kennedy was assassinated in:",
        optionA: "New York",
        optionB: "Austin",
        optionC: "Dallas",
        optionD: "Miami",
        answer: "Dallas",
        number: "3",
    },
    {
        prompt: "4. Who fought in the war of 1812?",
        optionA: "Andrew Jackson",
        optionB: "Arthur Wellesley",
        optionC: "Otto von Bismarck",
        optionD: "Napoleon",
        answer: "Andrew Jackson",
        number: "4",
    },
    {
        prompt: "5. Which general famously stated, 'I shall return?'",
        optionA: "Bull Halsey",
        optionB: "George Patton",
        optionC: "Douglas MacArthur",
        optionD: "Omar Bradley",
        answer: "Douglas MacArthur",
        number: "5",
    },
    {
        prompt: "6. American involvement in the Korean War took place in which decade?",
        optionA: "1970s",
        optionB: "1950s",
        optionC: "1920s",
        optionD: "1960s",
        answer: "1950s",
        number: "6",
    },
    {
        prompt: "7. The Battle of Hastings in 1066 was fought in which country?",
        optionA: "France",
        optionB: "Russia",
        optionC: "England",
        optionD: "Norway",
        answer: "England",
        number: "7",
    },
    {
        prompt: "8. The Magna Carta was published by the King of which country?",
        optionA: "France",
        optionB: "Austria",
        optionC: "Italy",
        optionD: "England",
        answer: "England",
        number: "8",
    },
    {
        prompt: "9. The first successful printing press was developed by this man.",
        optionA: "Johannes Gutenberg",
        optionB: "Benjamin Franklin",
        optionC: "Sir Isaac Newton",
        optionD: "Martin Luther",
        answer: "Johannes Gutenberg",
        number: "9",
    },
    {
        prompt: "10. The disease that ravaged and killed a third of Europe's population in the 14th century is known as:",
        optionA: "The White Death",
        optionB: "The Black Plague",
        optionC: "Smallpox",
        optionD: "The Bubonic Plague",
        answer: "The Bubonic Plague",
        number: "10",
    },
]